[PAINTBALLS FIRING]
HOWARD:
That was close.
(Raj:)God, I love the smell of paintballs
in the morning.
(Howard:)Yeah, still funny, Raj.
[PAINTBALLS FIRING]
(Leonard:)No way we can get to the ridge.
(Leonard:)The Chemistry Department
has us cut off.
(Howard:)What about the creek bed?
(Sheldon:)The Pharmacology Department
controls that.
(Sheldon:)And they're all hopped up
on experimental steroids.
(Raj:)That's it then, we're doomed.
Time to acknowledge
that we are paying the price...
...for some failing to attend Physics
Department paintball strategy meeting.
(Howard:)I told you, my mom has spider veins.
(Howard:)I had to take her to the laser clinic.
(Sheldon:)And I told you I wanted
to see a doctor's note.
(Raj:)We need a plan.
How about Operation Hammer of the Gods?
(Leonard:)Which one is Hammer of the Gods?
We hide in the parking lot
and ambush people when they come to pee.
No, the dumpsters are deep
in Astronomy Department territory.
(Leonard:)Shouldn't be a problem,
Venus is up during the day.